{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Garage Door Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40063/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40063,"taskName":"Garage Door - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Garage Door","xmTaskDescriptor":"Garage Door Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":97,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Garage Door automatic wood vinyl","textMessagingName":"Garage Door","rolloverLongDesc":"For when no door currently exists or when the owner wants to completely replace the old door \u0026 associated tracks \u0026 mechanisms.","rolloverShortDesc":"Note separate category for repair.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Garage Door.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Garage Door Installation \u0026 Replacement \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install New Garage Door","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":36,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Garage Door Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Garage Door - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Garage Door Installation Project","urlName":"Garage-Door-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Garage Door Installation Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Cost \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Garage Door, automatic, vinyl, overhead, fiberglass, tracks","emcCategoryOid":-12036,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":386,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40063/":{"taskOID":40063,"originalTaskOID":40063,"setID":386,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5588,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Garage Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which kind of garage door do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5718,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Single car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2041,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Double car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Double car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4992,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"RV garage door","answerDisplayText":"RV garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5077,"questionDisplayText":"Type of garage door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of garage door would you like? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3755,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Masonite","answerDisplayText":"Masonite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1751,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Custom (wood application)","answerDisplayText":"Custom (wood application)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5534,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sectional","answerDisplayText":"Sectional","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6369,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tilt-up","answerDisplayText":"Tilt-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4698,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Plain glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Plain glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1853,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Decorative glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Decorative glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5078,"questionDisplayText":"Need garage door opener?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want a garage door opener installed with your new garage door?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7185,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, need new system installed","answerDisplayText":"Yes, need new system installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7184,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yes, need existing system re-installed","answerDisplayText":"Yes, need existing system re-installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5588,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of Garage Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which kind of garage door do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5718,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Single car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2041,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Double car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Double car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4992,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"RV garage door","answerDisplayText":"RV garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5718,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Single car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Single car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2041,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Double car garage door","answerDisplayText":"Double car garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4992,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"RV garage door","answerDisplayText":"RV garage door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5077,"questionDisplayText":"Type of garage door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of garage door would you like? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3755,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Masonite","answerDisplayText":"Masonite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1751,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Custom (wood application)","answerDisplayText":"Custom (wood application)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5534,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sectional","answerDisplayText":"Sectional","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6369,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tilt-up","answerDisplayText":"Tilt-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4698,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Plain glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Plain glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1853,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Decorative glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Decorative glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2427,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3755,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Masonite","answerDisplayText":"Masonite","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1751,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Custom (wood application)","answerDisplayText":"Custom (wood application)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5534,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Sectional","answerDisplayText":"Sectional","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6369,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Tilt-up","answerDisplayText":"Tilt-up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4698,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Plain glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Plain glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1853,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Decorative glass panels","answerDisplayText":"Decorative glass panels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5078,"questionDisplayText":"Need garage door opener?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want a garage door opener installed with your new garage door?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7185,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, need new system installed","answerDisplayText":"Yes, need new system installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7184,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yes, need existing system re-installed","answerDisplayText":"Yes, need existing system re-installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7185,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Yes, need new system installed","answerDisplayText":"Yes, need new system installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7184,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Yes, need existing system re-installed","answerDisplayText":"Yes, need existing system re-installed","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":203064,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Looking for Parts Only","answerDisplayText":"Looking for Parts Only","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}